{
    "id": "616cc46431ea45f2ae3a9276732e38a7",
    "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Shakespeare is greater than ………………… playwright.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "any other"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2b0ca73491494c0cbcd6e305f803758c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ..................... than I.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ab1ef0a6e17643f28762498e463eed3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………….. than I am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more older",
                "older",
                "elder"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e967e289222b4880bf023c1b997f4279"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the ..................... . of the two routes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shorter",
                "shortest",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0561b11cdae14386ad8dca40f402a385"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the ...................... decision.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wisest",
                "most wisest",
                "most wise"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3f3fe6e92ace4ee88fcb93057a4bd623"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hercules was stronger than .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "any man",
                "any other man",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0d77f559cbf44e05a9e31632b17b2105"
        },
        {
            "question": "Of the two evils choose the ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b203dc676f4e4813816e012f92253d16"
        },
        {
            "question": "His clothes are superior …………………. mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ad03dde858b44b6a86800c48525cac5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Health is ...................... wealth",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "preferable to",
                "more preferable to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1106513675e74aa5aae354621a8ee286"
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer walking ………………… riding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "than",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2d07cdc3b91f403c8cd471aebc41ed29"
        }
    ]
}